The tip volume problem
Real-time operational picture
Every incoming tip is scored by AI
and assigned a priority tier — from
standard up to P1 Critical for active
victim situations.
One-click critical filter
Select the first tip. The detail pane
shows the NCMEC report data, AI analysis,
and circuit-specific legal guidance.
The tier badge reflects the scoring rationale
— here, age indicators and distress language
elevated this to P1 Critical.
Wilson v. Jessup compliance
The system enforces this automatically. No investigator
can accidentally open a blocked file.
Legal notes are generated per tip, citing
your circuit's case law. This language drops
directly into your warrant application.
Integrated warrant workflow
Once the judge grants the warrant, blocked
files unblock automatically. Full chain of custody
is logged.
Bundle deduplication
CyberTip Triage